http://www.schwarzins.com/privacy-policy

Blog
facebooktwitterlinked_in A Seeman Holtz Property & Casualty Company
SCHWARZ INSURANCE AGENCY, INC.Privacy Notice (01/01/2002)
At Schwarz Insurance Agency, Inc., maintaining customers’ trust and confidence is a high priority.  That is why we want to protect your privacy when we collect and use information about you, and why we take measures to safeguard that information.Chapter INS 25 of the Wisconsin Administrative Code generally prohibits any licenses of the Office of the Commissioner of Insurance, directly or through its affiliates, from sharing nonpublic personal information about you with a non-affiliated third party unless the institution provides you with a notice of its privacy policies and practices, such as the type of information that it collects about you and the categories of persons or entities to whom it may be disclosed.  In compliance with the Wisconsin Administrative Code, we are providing you with this document, which notifies you of the privacy policies and practices of Schwarz Insurance Agency, Inc.
OUR PRIVACY POLICIES AND PRACTICES
Information we collect.  We collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources:•    Information we receive from you on application or other forms.•    Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates or others.•    Information we receive from a consumer reporting agency.Information we may disclose to third parties:•    We do not disclose nonpublic personal information about our customers or former customers to anyone, except for persons or entities involved in securing insurance products or servicing and administering those products on your behalf.  We may disclose information we collect about our customers or former customers with other insurance agencies with whom we have a joint marketing agreement in order to better service our consumers and customers.Non-affiliated third parties to whom disclosures may be made:•    We disclose nonpublic personal information about you only to non-affiliated third parties such as insurance carriers, strictly for underwriting purposes.Our practices regarding information confidentiality and security:•    We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information in order to provide products or services to you.  We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to guard your nonpublic personal information.Reservation of the right to disclose information in unforeseen circumstances:•    In connection with the potential sale or transfer of its interests, Schwarz Insurance Agency, Inc. reserves the right to sell or transfer your information (including but not limited to your address, name, age, sex, zip code, state and country of residency and other information that you provide through other communications) to a third party entity that (1) concentrates its business in a similar practice or service; (2) agrees to be Schwarz Insurance Agency, Inc. successor in interests with regard to the maintenance and protection of the information collected; and (3) agrees to the obligations of this privacy statement.Amendment to Privacy Notice and Privacy Policy:•    We reserve the right to amend, modify or change at any time and for any reason, our privacy policies and this Privacy Notice.  In any such events, we will provide an amended Privacy Notice to you.
Sincerely,                                                                            Schwarz Insurance Agency, Inc.
Powered by Hits In A Box Pro
Copyright © 2020 Schwarz Insurance All Rights Reserved.    P: 800.552.8942  |  F: 608.643.3249      Privacy Policy  |  Contact Us
